Guide to the Time Inc. Advertising Promotion and Circulation Promotion Files 1922-2004 (bulk, 1923-1989) MS 3009-RG 21
New-York Historical Society
- Time: Education Department: Summer Review Quiz, 1945-1959 (Offsite-box 3669, Folder 8-9)
- Time: Education Department: Time Classroom Editions, 1943-1947 (Offsite-box 3669, Folder 10)
- Time: Education Department: Vacation Review Quiz, 1960-1965 (Offsite-box 3669, Folder 11)
- Time: Education Department: Miscellaneous, 1928-1953 (Offsite-box 3669, Folder 12-29)
- Time: Education Department: Miscellaneous, 1950s, 1960 (Offsite-box 3691, Folder 31-33)
- Time: Education Department: Miscellaneous, 1953-1959 (Offsite-box 3670, Folder 1-17)
- Time: Education Department: Miscellaneous, 1959-1963 (Offsite-box 3671, Folder 1-16)
- Time: Education Department: Miscellaneous, 1961-1966, 1977-1979 (Offsite-box 3692, Folder 1-3)
- Time: Education Department: Miscellaneous, 1964-1973 (Offsite-box 3672, Folder 1-18)
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container: "With Me Today. 14-min. interview, Alberse/Ross/Gerard. Time-Life International. Released 5/6/66."
  Includes information label: "With Me Today. Interview #138. Participants: Norman P. Ross, V.P. and Director of Educational R&D of the General Learning Corp.; Dr. Ralph Gerard, Prof. of Biological Sciences, Univ. of Cal at Irvine, and Jim Alberse, TLI. Subject: The wedding of journalism and electronics in the service of education. Length: 14 min."
- Time: Education Department: Miscellaneous, 1973-1991 (Offsite-box 3673, Folder 1-13)
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side 1: "Time Education Program. 'The Most Amazing 60 Years in History.' Running time 29:07. Side 1. Copyright 1983 Time Inc." Label on Side 2: "Time Education Program. 'The Most Amazing 60 Years in History.' Running time 26:06. Side 2. Copyright 1983 Time Inc."
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side 1 and 2: "Time Education Program. 'Martin Luther King Jr.: Chronicle of a Dream.' Running time 30:00. Copyright 1985 Time Inc."
- Time Canada: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Inserts, 1951-1971 (Offsite-box 3673, Folder 14-33)
- Time Canada: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Inserts, 1972-1975 (Offsite-box 3674, Folder 1-4)
- Time Canada: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Inserts, Miscellaneous, 1964-1969 (Offsite-box 3674, Folder 5-6)
- Time Canada: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Space Ads and Inserts, 1957-1958, 1967, 1971 (Offsite-box 3674, Folder 7-10)
- Time Canada: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Billings, 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 3674, Folder 11-13)
- Time Canada: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1969-1974 (Offsite-box 3674, Folder 14-17)
- Time Canada: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1948-1970 (Offsite-box 3674, Folder 18-39)
- Time Canada: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1974 (Offsite-box 3675, Folder 1)
- Time Canada: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1947-1957 (Offsite-box 3675, Folder 2-12)
- Time International: Advertisers Lists: General, 1948-1969 (Offsite-box 3675, Folder 13)
- Time International: Advertisers Lists: Canadian Edition, 1943-1968 (Offsite-box 3675, Folder 14)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Ads: General, 1941-1968 (Offsite-box 3675, Folder 15-32)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Ads: Copy Policy, 1947 (Offsite-box 3676, Folder 1)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Ads: World Trade Campaign, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 3676, Folder 2)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Ads: World Trade Campaign, 1946-1948 (Offsite-box 3692, Folder 4-5)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Ads, Foreign: Australia, 1950-1960 (Offsite-box 3676, Folder 3)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Ads, Foreign: Brazil, 1950-1960 (Offsite-box 3676, Folder 4)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Ads, Foreign: Canada, 1950-1960 (Offsite-box 3676, Folder 5-6)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Ads, Foreign: Germany, 1950-1960 (Offsite-box 3676, Folder 7)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Ads, Foreign: Great Britain, 1950-1960 (Offsite-box 3676, Folder 8)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Ads, Foreign: Latin America, 1950-1960 (Offsite-box 3676, Folder 9)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Ads, Foreign: "Time Differential" Campaign, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 3676, Folder 10)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Ads, Foreign: Time-Life International Campaign in Fortune, 1960-1963 (Offsite-box 3676, Folder 11)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Advertising Directors' Memos, 1961-1967 (Offsite-box 3676, Folder 12-13)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Direct Mail, 1941-1951 (Offsite-box 3676, Folder 14-22)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Direct Mail, 1946-1947, 1962-1969 (Offsite-box 3692, Folder 6-15)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Direct Mail, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 3677, Folder 1-14)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Direct Mail, 1955-1959 (Offsite-box 3678, Folder 1-14)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Direct Mail, 1959-1963 (Offsite-box 3679, Folder 1-14)
  Includes reprints of Time Latin America's Hemisphere section, a four-page news section mailed to business executives from 1961 to 1963.
  Includes two copies of a reproduction Time practice dummy ("specimen issue") dated December 22, 1922, previously unpublished before 1963.
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Direct Mail, 1963-1967 (Offsite-box 3680, Folder 1-16)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Direct Mail, 1968-1969, 1973 (Offsite-box 3681, Folder 1-8)
  Includes Birthday of a Nation: The Story of Canada's Centennial, 1968.
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: Atlantic Edition, 1943-1959 (Offsite-box 3681, Folder 9-12)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: Canadian Edition, 1943-1950 (Offsite-box 3681, Folder 13-17)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: Latin American Edition, 1941-1949 (Offsite-box 3682, Folder 1-4)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: Pacific Edition, 1946-1953 (Offsite-box 3682, Folder 5-6)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: Miscellaneous, 1946-1961 (Offsite-box 3682, Folder 7-15)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: Miscellaneous, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 3683, Folder 1-14)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: Miscellaneous, 1966-1969 (Offsite-box 3684, Folder 1-13)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Research Reports: Miscellaneous, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 3685, Folder 1-8)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Sales Memos, 1951-1958 (Offsite-box 3686, Folder 1-15)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Sales Memos, 1959-1964 (Offsite-box 3687, Folder 1-14)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Sales Memos, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 3688, Folder 1-14)
- Time International: Advertising Promotion: Sales Memos, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 3689, Folder 1-12)
- Time International: Circulation Promotion: Inserts, 1954, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3689, Folder 13-15)
- Time International: Circulation Promotion: Inserts, 1971-1975 (Offsite-box 3690, Folder 1-4)
- Time International: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Billings, 1973 (Offsite-box 3690, Folder 5)
- Time International: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1941-1974 (Offsite-box 3690, Folder 6-20)
- Time International: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1941-1972 (Offsite-box 3690, Folder 21-36)
- Time International: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1945-1962 (Offsite-box 3690, Folder 37-51)
- TV-Cable Week: Advertising Promotion, 1983 (Offsite-box 3690, Folder 52-54)
- TV-Cable Week: Advertising Promotion, 1983 (Offsite-box 3692, Folder 16)
- TV-Cable Week: Circulation Promotion, 1983 (Offsite-box 3690, Folder 55)
- TV-Cable Week: Circulation Promotion, 1983 (Offsite-box 3692, Folder 17)